好吧 走吧 我带你回去
Yeah. Come on, I'll give you a ride.
象征了你们不朽的爱情
Symbolizes your eternal love.
我现在宣布你们结为夫妻
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
我们结婚啦!
We did it!
我真高兴你们能见证这一时刻!
I'm so glad you guys could watch!
我们在评论区里写上"甚是美好"吧
We'll say it was beautiful in the comment section.
不 不 不 等一会
No, no, no. Hang on.
新浪该抱着新娘跨过门槛的
I believe I'm supposed to carry you across the threshold.
你行吗你?
Can you?
你觉得每次Sheldon在电视机前睡着了
Who do you think carries Sheldon to bed
是谁把他抱上床睡觉的?
when he falls asleep in front of the TV?
好吧 那你抱吧
Okay, let's do it.
- 你行不行啊?  - 我行的!
- You gonna make it?  - I'm okay!
行啊你!
Nicely done!
谢谢
Thank you.
我总算没有
Finally, there's a Mrs. Hofstadter
让Hofstadter夫人失望
who isn't disappointed in me.
夜色还早
Well, the night is still young.
你还好吗?
Everything all right?
还好吧 我想
Yeah. I guess.
有事就说啊
Just tell me.
只是 在吻你的时候
It's just, when we were kissing,
我总是忍不住会脑补到你吻那个女孩的场景
I couldn't help but picture you with that other girl.
哦 不
Oh, no.
不 拜托
No, come on.
不是说好
I have a friend in you.
是好朋友吗
You said so.
说得对 当我刚才没说吧
You're right. Just forget it.
对啊
Yeah.
好吧 听着 呃
Okay, listen. Uh...
别把我和她亲吻的场景想象的很性感
If you're imagining that it was sexy.
不是的
It wasn't.
我们都喝醉了 她身上一股烟味
We... we were both drunk, and she smelled like an ashtray.
那船还摇摇晃晃的 弄得我还磕到了她牙齿
The boat was moving a lot, so I chipped her tooth.
你觉得内疚吗?
Did you feel guilty?
不会 她上了牙科保险的
No, she had dental insurance.
你吻了她觉得内疚吗
Did you feel guilty after kissing her?
当然啦 吻她那一瞬间我就觉得很内疚了
Yes. I felt guilty as soon as it happened.
到现在每一次一见到她我就觉得很内疚
I feel guilty every time I see her.
每一次见到她是什么意思?
What do you mean, every time you see her?
我... 说的话什么意思来着?
What... do I mean?